[{"answer": "Yes, always.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 12, "question": "It was a consensual mutual relationship sexually speaking, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 11}, {"answer": "Look, I've been on a mission.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "But are you just going to take that or do you believe there is a genuine prospect of achieving this?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "I think many people don't really realize the difference between handgun injury and assault weapons injury.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Do you think people were surprised by what you were telling them?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Well, I think we all want to try to keep criminals from going and getting guns.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Is your belief still that the only answer to America's gun violence is more guns?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Well, obviously they were all killed.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Look, Piers, let me just ask you a question.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Do they to you?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "The semiautomatic hunting rifles can fire exactly the same number of bullets per minute as your AR-15.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "So if you remove hunting from the equation, what are you left with as a purpose for these weapons?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "I mean, I have written papers on it.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "Mr. Lott do you know how many mass shootings there have been in the last 30 years in America?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Do you know what weapons were used in those mass shootings?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "OK, Before I will get to that question, which I will get to, I want to go and deal with the points you were just raising.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "What I don't understand from all the expertise you bring to this, is - and I don't want to put words in your mouth -- but of all the 35 proposals President Obama has put forward, which ones would you actually agree with in terms of introducing more gun safety in America?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "It depends on how you define them.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Do you know how many there have been since the gun ban was brought in?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Okay.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Do you know how many there have been in Australia since they brought in the gun ban?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Now, how many have there been since 1996?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "I already said it a couple of times.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "How many since '96?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "There was one before, and there haven't been any after.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "-- following massacres like Sandy Hook -", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Why am I on?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "They have seen zero mass shootings in one country.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Why am I on?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Germany had both of their shootings in the last 10 years.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "How many in the last ten years have been killed by guns in Germany?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Again, what you have --", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "No, no!", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Do you know the answer to the country that you raised as an example of proof of your argument?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "OTT: The point is it was even lower before --", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "How many people were murdered in Britain last year with guns?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "It makes more sense to talk about murder rates, to deal with differences in populations --", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "How many?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "In theory, if you could fix the problems with the current background system, that would be great.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Do you believe in universal background checks for all guns in America?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "I don't think I supported any of the ones that he had.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "But of the 35 proposals for gun safety that the president is trying to bring in, how many of the 35 do you support?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Well, they are pretty serious if you're the father of a boy who has been blown to pieces.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Were they?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Have you ever heard a case quite like this?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "Well, I think the prosecution is mishandling this case completely.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Or am I misreading this?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "I do, actually.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Marcia Clark, do you see a point to what is going on in this courtroom?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "Why not make them focus on the deliberate lies that are central to the facts in this case?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "130227pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "If you take him at face value in those private conversations he was having with fetishists, however ghastly the earlier material I read, is he a criminal?", "qSentId": 657}]